parslivetv.eu 2014-12-23

# Serial Privacy_policy - parslivetv.eu

### **Download free TV and Farsi1 HD Toolbar == >**

|   
---|---  
  
**Privacy Policy / Contact US**  
Farsi1HD takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.  
Routine Information Collection  
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
Where necessary, iranianlivetv uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.  
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.  
Controlling Your Privacy  
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.  
Contact Information  
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to info@free0098.com for further clarification.

**Latest added Series (Serialhaye amade shode, be tartib)**

* * *

 **Newest, First...

 Seriale Karadayi Part 211  
Salhaye Por MajaraPart 55  
 Dar Entezare Aftab Part 106  
 Roozi Roozegari Part 108

 Karadayi Zirnevis Fasl3 266

**

* * *

Copyright ©2010 free0098.com | Privacy Policy / Contact US| **FAQ / Soalha Va Javabha** [ ](http://www.countomat.de/77390.html "Countomat Webcounter und Webstatistik \(Statistik und Logfileanalyse, Counter\)")
